<resources>
    <string name="app_name">snooKounter</string>
    <string name="howtouse">The app is split up into 2 sides: one for each player.
        \nWhen it is your turn, <b>tap</b> any of the colored buttons on your side to increase the score by the amount equal to the ball.
            If you commit a foul, <b>hold</b> the white button to give the opponent 4 points,
            or the higher valued buttons if necessary.
        \nTo <b>undo</b> a score change, swipe vertically across the screen.
        \nAnd to <b>reset</b>, swipe in the same manner back and forth multiple times.
        \n<b>Extra note:</b> if necessary, you can also <b>hold</b> the red button to reduce your score by 2!
    </string>
    <string name="rules">The balls are placed on the table as shown in the <b>first picture</b>.
        \nThe white ball can be placed anywhere inside the D on the table.
        \n<b>The game plays as follows</b>: at the start of your turn, you have to pot any one of the <b>red</b> balls, and if you do,
            you move on to pot any of the other <b>colored</b> balls, and you repeat that afterwards - red, colored, red, colored, etc.
            Potted red balls are not brought back, but <b>potted colored balls are placed back to their original position.</b>
            If that is not possible, they are placed on the highest available spot, and if not that,
            then as close to their base position as possible.
        \nAfterwards, when all of the red balls are potted, colored balls are potted from lowest to highest
            (without placing them back of course). The player with the most points wins!
        \n<b>Which leads to scoring-</b> a potted ball is worth the number of points as shown in the <b>second picture.</b>
            If you do not touch/pot the right ball, your shot is considered a <b>foul</b>, and your opponent gets points-
            a minimum of 4 and as high as the incorrectly potted ball, up to 7, as well as the opportunity to place
            the cue ball wherever on the table.
        \n<b>Extra tidbits:</b> if only the black remains, and the score is even, a tie breaker happens, where
            it is played until someone either pots the black or fouls. And, calling a shot a <b>snooker</b> is when
            the ball that was meant to be hit was missed because there was no clear line of sight of the ball.
    </string>
    <string name="rules_ps">
        <i>p.s.: what is written here does ignore some specifics of the official rules - this was done to
            make it more accessible to newcomers (hopefully)</i>
    </string>
</resources>